+353 83 124 6901 arturcmjr@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/arturcmjr github.com/arturcmjr

ARTUR JUNIOR

Summary

Game developer with experience in art, programming, level design and more. Work with the unity engine to bring life to ideas. Experience with deploying and maintaining games on most used stores. Ability to create tools to help with the game development process.

Skill Highlights

Soft Skills

- Fast learner
- Self-starter
- Creative
- Critical thinking

Hard Skills

- Unity
- Blender
- Photoshop
- C#

Experience

Game Developer - 05/2017 to 07/2018

Roundstars, Brasilia, Brazil

- Worked on developing single-player and multiplayer board games. Coding core mechanism, search algorithms and bots Als. I've also designed interfaces for those games.
- Worked mainly with Unity and C# for game development. There I could also help with the creation of an API for a small social media.

Designer - 12/2018 to 10/2020 **ADRA Brasil**, Brasilia, Brazil

- Created art for fundraising campaigns for crises, design reports, and presentation slides with Photoshop, Illustrator, and other design software.
- There, I had the opportunity to develop a system to help to control the hot meals given to Venezuelan refugees.

Web Developer - 10/2020 to 09/2022

Adven.Tech, Remote, Brazil

- Worked developing web apps such as a stock management, event, e-commerce and other systems on client demand. I also helped to migrate legacy systems to modern technologies.
- Written clean and scalable code for the back and front end. Worked with popular technologies such as Angular, React, .NET, C#, SQL and others.

Education

- Graduation on Game Development 2018, IESB, Brasília, Brazil.
- Post-graduation at System Analysis and Development 2022, Descomplica, Remote.
- Post-graduation at Mobile Development 2022, Descomplica, Remote.